Jack Douglas Papers
Jack Douglas Papers
- Writings
  - Radio Scripts
    - The Pepsodent Program, starring Bob Hope
      - 1940 Dec 31, Preview, anno., 29 p. (Box 15)
      - 1940 Dec 31, rev., 26 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Jan 5, Preview 57 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Jan 7, revised, 26 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Jan 12, Preview, anno., 54 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Jan 14, revised, 26 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Jan 19, Preview, 56 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Jan 21, revised, 22 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Jan 26, Preview, 51 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Jan 28, revised, 24 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Feb 2, Preview, anno., 45 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Feb 4, revised, 24 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Feb 9, Preview, 44 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Feb 11, revised, 25 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Feb 16, Preview, rev., 41 p.; fragment, rev., 1 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Feb 18, revised, 24 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Feb 23, Preview, anno., 48 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Feb 25, revised, 24 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Mar 2, revised, 21 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Mar 16, Preview, anno., 52 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Mar 18, revised, 26 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Mar 23, Preview, 31 p. (Box 15)
      - 1941 Mar 25, revised, 24 p. (Box 16)
      - 1941 Mar 30, anno., rev., 51 p. (Box 16)
      - 1941 Apr 1, revised, 23 p. (Box 16)
      - 1941 Apr 6, revised, 42 p. (Box 16)
      - 1941 Apr 8, revised, 23 p. (Box 16)
      - 1941 Apr 13, Preview, 47 p. (Box 16)
      - 1941 Apr 15, revised, 23 p. (Box 16)
      - 1941 Apr 20, Preview, 43 p. (Box 16)
      - 1941 May 11, revised, 26 p. (Box 16)
      - 1941 May 13, revised, 25 p. (Box 16)
      - 1941 May 18, Preview, anno., 40 p. (Box 16)
      - 1941 May 20, revised, 24 p. (Box 16)
      - 1941 May 25, Preview, 46 p. (Box 16)
      - 1941 May 27, revised, 26 p. (Box 16)
      - 1941 Jun 1, Preview, anno., 47 p. (Box 16)
      - 1941, Misc. fragments, anno., rev., 208 p. (Box 16)
    - Tommy Riggs Show
      - Undated audition script, first draft, 24 p. (Box 17)
      - 1942 Jul 14, fragment, 3 p. (Box 17)
      - 1942 Jul 21, first revision, anno., 24 p. (Box 17)
      - 1942 Jul 21, 25 p. (Box 17)
      - 1942 Jul 21, incomplete, anno., 20 p. (Box 17)
      - 1942 Aug 4, anno., 22 p. (Box 17)
      - 1942 Aug 4, Second Revision, 9 p. (Box 17)
      - 1942 Aug 11, 20 p. (Box 17)
      - 1942 Aug 11, anno., 20 p. (Box 17)
      - 1942 Aug 11, Second Revision, 18 p. (Box 17)
      - 1942 Aug 18, 22 p. (Box 17)
      - 1942 Sep 1, fragment, 5 p. (Box 17)
      - 1942 Sep 29, 21 p. (Box 17)
      - 1942 Nov 20, 20 p. (Box 17)
      - 1942 Nov 27, revised, fragment, 8 p. (Box 17)
      - 1942 Dec 11, revised, 20 p. (Box 17)
      - Undated fragments, 1942; printed material, typescript, typescript copy rev. (Box 17)
    - The Borden Show, starring Tommy Riggs
      - 1946 May 10, rev., 21 p. (Box 17)
      - 1946 May 10, revised, rev., 24 p. (Box 17)
      - 1946 May 17, anno., 25 p. (Box 17)
      - 1946 May 24, 21 p. (Box 17)
      - 1946 May 24, fragment, typescript copy anno., 7 p. (Box 17)
    - Sealtest Village Store Program, starring Jack Carson
      - 1947 Dec 11, Preview, rev., 24 p. (Box 18)
      - 1947 Dec 11, revised, anno., 21 p. (Box 18)
      - 1947 Dec 18, revised, rev., 24 p. (Box 18)
      - 1947 Dec 25, anno., 24 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Jan 1, Preview, anno., rev., 28 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Jan 1, revised, 25 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Jan 8, first draft, anno., rev., 26 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Jan 8, revised, anno., rev., 23 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Jan 15, revised, anno., rev., 26 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Jan 22, Preview, anno., rev., 27 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Jan 22, revised, anno., rev., 25 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Jan 29, Preview, anno., 25 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Feb 5, Preview, anno., rev., 25 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Feb 5, revised, anno., 24 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Feb 12, rev., 28 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Feb 19, revised, rev., 23 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Feb 26, revised, rev., 27 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Mar 4, revised, anno., rev., 26 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Mar 11, draft revised, typescript copy., printed material, 31 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Mar 18, typescript copy., 17 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Mar 18, Preview, 26 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Mar 18, revised, anno., 24 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Mar 25, Preview, anno., 28 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Mar 25, revised, anno., 25 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Apr 1, Preview, 17 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Apr 1, Preview, rev., 23 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Apr 8, revised, anno., 25 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Apr 15, Preview, anno., 26 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Apr 15, revised, 24 p. (Box 18)
      - 1948 Apr 22, Preview, 17 p. (Box 19)
      - 1948 Apr 22, revised, 24 p. (Box 19)
      - 1948 Apr 29, Preview, 25 p. (Box 19)
      - 1948 Apr 29, revised, 25 p. (Box 19)
      - 1948 May 6, revised, anno., 26 p. (Box 19)
      - 1948 May 13, 23 p. (Box 19)
      - 1948 May 20, Preview, anno., rev., 24 p. (Box 19)
      - 1948 May 20, revised, 23 p. (Box 19)
      - 1948 Jun 3, revised, 21 p. (Box 19)
      - 1948 Jun 10, Preview, anno., 27 p. (Box 19)
      - 1948 Jun 10, revised anno., 24 p. (Box 19)
      - 1948 Jun 24, first draft, anno., 24 p. (Box 19)
      - 1948 Jun 24, revised, anno., 24 p. (Box 19)
      - 1948 Jul 1, revised, anno., 23 p. (Box 19)
      - Undated, 1948; typescript copy rev., 18 p.; typescript, typescript copy., 18 p. (Box 19)
    - Silver Theatre
      - "Who Done It?", 1940 Nov 10; typescript copy, 26 p.; typescript copy, 26 p.; first draft, rev., 35 p. (Box 19)
      - "Petticoat Fever," adaptation by Robert Riley Crutcher, 1941 Nov 2; typescript copy, anno., 24 p.; first draft, rev., 25 p. Second draft, rev., 29 p.; Third draft, anno., rev., 26 p. (Box 19)
    - Red Skelton Show
      - 1941 Oct 7, rev., 33 p. (Box 19)
      - 1941 Oct 14, anno., rev., 32 p. (Box 19)
      - 1941 Oct 14, revised, anno., rev., 24 p. (Box 19)
      - 1941 Oct 21, anno., rev., 30 p. (Box 19)
      - 1941 Oct 21, revised, anno., rev., 25 p. (Box 19)
      - 1941 Oct 26, anno., rev., 31 p. (Box 19)
      - 1941 Oct 28, revised, anno., rev., 31 p. (Box 19)
      - 1941 Nov 4, anno., rev., 30 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Nov 4, revised, rev., 25 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Nov 11, rev., 35 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Nov 11, revised, anno., rev., 27 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Nov 18, revised, rev., 25 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Nov 18, printed material, typescript copy., rev., 39 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Nov 25, anno., rev., 33 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Nov 25, revised, rev., 26 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Nov 30, anno., rev., 36 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Dec 2, revised, 25 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Dec 9, revised, anno., rev., 27 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Dec 9, anno., rev., 19 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Dec 16, revised, rev., 28 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Dec 16, anno., rev., 33 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Dec 23, anno., rev., 23 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Dec 23, revised, rev., 28 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Dec 30, revised, anno., rev., 26 p. (Box 20)
      - 1941 Dec 30, anno., rev., 30 p. (Box 20)
      - 1942 Jan 6, anno., rev., 23 p. (Box 20)
      - 1942 Jan 6, revised, rev., 26 p. (Box 20)
      - 1942 Jan 13, revised, anno., rev., 27 p. (Box 20)
      - 1942 Jan 13, rev., 25 p. (Box 20)
      - 1942 Jan 20, revised, anno., rev., 26 p. (Box 20)
      - 1942 Jan 27, revised, rev., 26 p. (Box 20)
      - 1942 Jan 27, anno., rev., 26 p. (Box 20)
      - 1942 Feb 3, revised, anno., 28 p. (Box 20)
      - 1942 Feb 3, rev., 32 p. (Box 20)
      - 1942 Feb 10, revised, anno., 26 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Feb 10, rev., 42 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Feb 15, revised, rev., 27 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Feb 15, anno., 39 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Feb 22, revised, anno., 34 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Feb 22, anno., 38 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Mar 8, revised, anno., 27 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Mar 8, anno., 37 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Mar 15, 27 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Mar 15, anno., 31 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Mar 22, revised, anno., rev., 26 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Mar 29, revised, rev., 28 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Apr 4, revised, 24 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Apr 12, revised, rev., 30 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Apr 26, revised, 28 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 May 3, revised, anno., 29 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 May 17, revised, 28 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 May 31, revised, 25 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 May 31, 32 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Sep 13, revised, 29 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Sep 15, 36 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Sep 20, revised, anno., 31 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Sep 20, 43 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Sep 21, fragment, 8 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Sep 27, anno., 32 p. (Box 21)
      - 1942 Oct 11, revised, 31 p. (Box 22)
      - 1942 Oct 11, rev., 41 p. (Box 22)
      - 1942 Oct 18, revised, 29 p. (Box 22)
      - 1942 Nov 15, anno., 38 p. (Box 22)
      - 1942 Nov 29, 43 p. (Box 22)
      - 1942 Nov 29, revised, 29 p. (Box 22)
      - 1942 Dec 6, fragment, revised, anno., 6 p. (Box 22)
      - 1942 Dec 6, 46 p. (Box 22)
      - 1942 Dec 8, 31 p. (Box 22)
      - 1942 Dec 13, 46 p. (Box 22)
      - 1942 Dec 20, 42 p. (Box 22)
      - 1942 Dec 27, 47 p. (Box 22)
      - Undated and untitled, 1942; 12 folders (Box 22)
      - Clem, 1942?; Outline, fragment, typescript copy, 14 p. (Box 22)
      - "Command Performance...Junior", 1942?; 7 p. (Box 22)
      - Screen Guild "Tight Shoes," Red Skelton, 1942?; Copy, typescript, typescript copy, 22 p. (Box 22)
      - 1943 Jan 10, 49 p. (Box 23)
      - 1943 Jan 17, 41 p. (Box 23)
      - 1943 Jan 24, rev. 49 p. (Box 23)
      - 1943 Jan 31, 46 p. (Box 23)
      - 1943 Feb 16, Second Commercial, typescript copy rev., 2 p. (Box 23)
      - 1943 Feb 28, 44 p. (Box 23)
      - 1943 Mar 7, 37 p. (Box 23)
      - 1943 Mar 7, 32 p. (Box 23)
      - 1943 Mar 21, rev., 26 p. (Box 23)
      - 1943 May 16, 27 p. (Box 23)
      - Undated "Slice of Life" scenes, 1943; anno., 13 p.; 4 folders (Box 23)
      - Undated fragment, 1943; typescript, printed material, holo., typescript, (Box 23)
      - Undated miscellaneous fragments, 1943; typescript copy, printed material, rev. 165 p. (Box 23)
    - Sunbrite Smile Parade
      - 1939 Jun 1, rev. 25 p. (Box 24)
      - 1939 Jun 29, fragment, anno., 3 p. (Box 24)
      - 1939 Jul 6, anno., rev., 24 p. (Box 24)
      - 1939 Jul 13, additional material, typescript repro., 10 p. (Box 24)
      - 1939 Jul 20, 27 p. (Box 24)
      - 1939 Aug 3, anno., 26 p. (Box 24)
      - 1939 Aug 10, anno., 27 p. (Box 24)
      - 1939 Aug 17, 23 p. (Box 24)
      - 1939?, anno., rev., 26 p. (Box 24)
    - What's New
      - 1944 Jan 8, Routine, Second Revision, rev., 22 p. (Box 24)
      - 1944 Jan 15, rev., 29 p. (Box 24)
    - Jack Douglas spots
      - Undated, typescript rev., 11 p. (Box 24)
      - Undated, typescript anno., rev., 11 p. (Box 24)
      - Undated, typescript rev., 6 p. (Box 24)
      - Undated, typescript 7 p. (Box 24)
      - Undated, miscellaneous pages, typescript, typescript copy rev., 42 p. (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous radio scripts
      - "Command Performance", undated; 25 p. (Box 24)
      - "Love Is News", undated; fragment, 9 p. (Box 24)
      - "Nit Wit Court", Jul 25, 1944; revised, 24 p. (Box 24)
      - "The Show-Off", [1940]; typescript, 45 p. (Box 24)
      - Ginny Simms Show, May 3, 1946; anno., 9 p. (Box 24)
      - "This Is My Best," "Mlle. Irene the Great", Mar 6, 1945; rev., 28 p. (Box 24)
      - "Wit's End," by Alan Smith, undated; typescript copy, 11 p. (Box 24)
  - Television Scripts
    - Broadway Open House
      - 1951 Jun 19, fragments, anno., 14 p. (Box 24)
      - 1951 Jul 20, fragments, anno., 10 p. (Box 24)
      - 1951 Jul 20, fragments, typescript rev., 4 p. (Box 24)
      - 1951 Jul 20, anno., 13 p. (Box 24)
      - 1951 Jul 24, anno., 13 p. (Box 24)
      - 1951 Jul 26, anno., 19 p. (Box 24)
    - George Gobel
      - 1954 Oct 2, 31 p. (Box 24)
      - 1954 Oct 2, 46 p. (Box 24)
      - 1954 Oct 9, 45 p. (Box 24)
      - 1954 Oct 16, typescript rev., 19 p. (Box 24)
      - 1954 Oct 16, anno., 32 p. (Box 24)
      - 1954 Nov 6, anno., 38 p. (Box 25)
      - 1954 Nov 13, anno., 38 p. (Box 25)
      - 1954 Nov 27, anno., 26 p. (Box 25)
      - 1954 Dec 4, 32 p. (Box 25)
      - 1954 Dec 4, fragment, typescript copy, 5 p. (Box 25)
      - 1954 Dec 11, typescript copy, 28 p. (Box 25)
      - 1954 Dec 11, anno., 32 p. (Box 25)
      - 1954 Dec 25, 31 p. (Box 25)
      - 1955 Jan 8, anno., 33 p. (Box 25)
      - 1955 Jan 22, anno., 36 p. (Box 25)
      - 1955 Jan 29, anno., 41 p. (Box 25)
      - 1955 Feb 5, anno., 36 p. (Box 25)
      - 1955 Mar 19, anno., 37 p. (Box 25)
      - 1955 Misc. fragments, typescript, typescript copy, printed material, 39 p. (Box 25)
    - Peter Lind Hayes and Mary Healy
      - 1950 Dec 21, typescript copy, 8 p. (Box 25)
      - 1950 Dec 28, typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 25)
      - 1951 Jan 11, typescript copy, 36 p. (Box 25)
      - 1951 Jan 11, anno., rev., 39 p. (Box 25)
      - 1951 Jan 18, typescript, typescript copy, rev., 6 p. (Box 25)
      - 1951 Jan 18, fragment, 3 p. (Box 25)
      - 1951 Jan 25, typescript rev., 12 p. (Box 25)
      - 1951 Jan 25, typescript copy, 26 p. (Box 25)
      - 1951 Jan 25, anno., 12p. (Box 25)
      - 1951 Jan, holo. notes, 10 p. (Box 25)
      - 1951 Jan fragments, typescript rev., printed material, 7 p. (Box 25)
      - 1951 Feb 1, 21 p. (Box 25)
      - 1951 Feb 8, typescript rev., 25 p. (Box 25)
      - ca. 1951, 4 folders (Box 25)
      - ca. 1951, 6 folders (Box 26)
    - Beatrice Lillie Show
      - 1951 May 13, 63 p. (Box 26)
      - 1951 May 13, Ouija Board, revised, 12 p. (Box 26)
      - 1951 May 13, Street Scene, 12 p. (Box 26)
    - Red Skelton Show
      - New Year's Show, 1951; typescript copy rev., 4 p. (Box 26)
      - Gimmicks for Poet and Peasant", 1951 Oct; typescript copy rev., 2 p. (Box 26)
      - 1951 Nov 1 meeting, ideas for bits, typescript copy, 5 p. (Box 26)
      - 1951 Nov 5 meeting, ideas for bits, typescript copy, 13 p. (Box 26)
      - 1951 Nov 9 meeting, ideas for bits typescript, 1 p. (Box 26)
      - 1952 Jan 8 meeting, additional notes on "Smoothola" and "Spectre of the Rose," typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 26)
      - 1952? Jan 20, ideas for bits, typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 26)
      - 1954 Dec 14, first draft, 34 p. (Box 26)
      - 1954 Dec 21, 31 p. (Box 26)
      - 1954 Dec 28, first draft; anno., 31 p. (Box 26)
      - 1955 Jan 5, first draft, anno., 36 p. (Box 26)
      - Undated, 1955
        - Ideas for bits, typescript copy, 7 p. (Box 26)
        - "Intro to Gal Swingers", typescript copy rev., 6 p. (Box 26)
        - McPugg sketch, untitled, typescript copy, 8 p. (Box 26)
        - "Send Out Skelton Service", anno., rev., 7 p. (Box 26)
        - "T.V. Spy Bit", typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 26)
        - "Three Stages of Married Life", typescript copy 3 p. (Box 26)
        - "What to do in Case of a Burglar", typescript copy, 3 p. (Box 26)
        - Schedule of Television Shows, Nov 4-25, typescript copy, 2 p. (Box 26)
    - The Soldiers
      - 1955 Jul 16, 46 p. (Box 26)
      - 1955 Jul 16, revised, 56 p. (Box 26)
      - 1955 Jul 16, fragment, anno., 5 p. (Box 26)
      - 1955 Jul 23, Original, 40 p. (Box 26)
      - 1955 Jul 23, As Broadcast, anno., 57 p. (Box 26)
      - 1955 Jul 23, As Broadcast, rev., 54 p. (Box 26)
      - 1955 Aug 5, 40 p. (Box 26)
      - 1955 Aug 6, Second Revision, 57 p. (Box 27)
      - 1955 Aug 13, 44 p. (Box 27)
      - 1955 Aug 27, 45 p. (Box 27)
      - Undated fragment, 1955; revised, 16 p.; fragment, some typescript, typescript copy rev., 35 p. (Box 27)
    - Ed Wynn Show
      - 1950 Nov 15, first draft, 53 p. (Box 27)
      - 1950 Nov 15, fragments, typescript, typescript copy, rev., 6 p. (Box 27)
      - 1950 Nov 15, commercial, typescript copy rev., 5 p. (Box 27)
      - Undated lines for comedy commercial, 1955; typescript rev., 2 p. (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous television scripts
      - "Commercially Speaking" sketch, undated; typescript copy, 6 p. (Box 27)
  - Motion picture scripts
    - The Ghost Breakers
      - Fragment, 1939; typescript copy, 13p. (Box 27)
      - Sequences A and B, Dec 27, 1939; anno., 81 p., (Box 27)
    - Louisiana Purchase
      - Sequences A, B, C, D, E, and F, [1941]; typescript copy, 82 p., (Box 27)
    - My Favorite Blond
      - Sequences A-F, [1941]; typescript copy, 82 p. (Box 27)
      - Sequences A-F, Aug 22, 1941; anno., 140 p., (Box 27)
    - A Night at Earl Carroll's
      - Brenda and Cobina Sequence, [1940?]; typescript copy, 6 p. (Box 27)
      - "Show Business," Brenda and Cobina Sequences, [1940]; fragment, typescript copy, 8.p. (Box 27)
      - Final white, Apr 10, 1940; anno., 94 p., (Box 27)
    - Nothing But the Truth
      - Sequences A and B, Feb 17, 1941; anno., 67 p., (Box 28)
      - Sequences A-C, Mar 20, 1941; anno., 109 p., (Box 28)
      - Sequences C-E, [1941]; typescript copy, 48 p., (Box 28)
      - Sequences D and E, Mar 22, 1941; 39 p., (Box 28)
      - Sequence A, Mar 29, 1941; 41 p., (Box 28)
      - Sequences C-E, Apr 4, 1941; anno., 84 p., (Box 28)
    - Road to Singapore, Sep 22, 1939; second buff script, 111 p., (Box 28)
    - Road to Zanzibar, Oct 10, 1940; anno., 119 p. (Box 28)
    - The Time, the Place, and the Girl, Mar 21, 1945; Second Revision, final, 123 p. (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous motion picture scripts
      - His Majesty the Baby, Nov 15, 1935; fragment, typescript, 5 p. (Box 28)
      - Ice-Capades by Jack Townley and Robert Harari, May 26, 1941; Estimating script, 78 p. (Box 28)
      - I'll Take Manila by Harry Clork [sic], Nov 4, 1941; typescript copy, printed material, anno., rev., 104 p. (Box 28)
      - Radio Revels of 1942 by Dorcas Cochran and Arthur V. Jones, May 1, 1941; 112 p. (Box 28)
      - Show Business by Edmund Hartmann and Bert Lawrence, Jan 28, 1941; Estimating script, second draft, 92 p. (Box 29)
      - Show Business by Joseph Quillan and Dorothy Bennett, Oct 15, 1943; with additional dialogue by Irving Elinson, Final script, 153 p. (Box 29)
  - Novel
    - The Harvey Girls, by Eleanore Griffin and William Rankin, undated; 94 p. (Box 29)
  - Play
    - Untitled and unidentified, [1954?]; typescript, typescript copy, printed material, rev., 56 p. (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous fragments (Box 29)